Welcome.
This video will help you
understand how to create orders
in Einstein 2.
You will learn the following
how to create orders from
scratch, how to save templates
and order drafts
edit submitted orders
to start, go to your account at
the Einstein To website and
select Create Order on Dashboard.
Also, you can create it on
Order Management.
All orders that you have
already added are listed on
this page.
After you select Create Order,
you can see three tabs order
details, credentials and bill
rates.
On Order details, select the
order type and enter needed
information into the required
fields to specify details.
Also, you can add supporting
documents here
to have options available in
Region, Location, Department,
and Skill Fields.
Make sure you have added
relevant data in Settings or an
administrator configured it for
you.
Credentials let you add
different certificates,
checklists licenses, and other
materials to your order.
To do it, select Add Unassigned
Credentials and pick available
options on the list.
The credentials table can be
automatically prepopulated with
data based on the chosen region,
location, department, and skill.
It is possible if you have
respective fields mapped in
Settings
on Bill Rates.
You can manually attach new
bill rates.
To do it, select Add Bill rate
and provide data.
Also, data can be prepopulated
if you have fields mapped in
Settings and select Needed
Options in Region, Location,
Department, and Skill Fields.
On Order Details
after you have added all the
necessary information, you are
ready to submit the order.
Besides the immediate
submission, you can save the
order as a draft and get back
to it later, or save the order
as a template and reuse it as
many times as you need.
To access necessary orders
faster.
Go to respective tabs.
You search or apply filters on
Order Management.
All submitted orders get the
Open status.
You can edit the order if the
submitted order still has this
status type.
To do it, find the needed
record on the list and select
Edit next to it.
Change data and submit changes.
Please note if you edit region,
location, Department or Skill
fields, data will be changed
based on your Edits on
Credentials and Bill Rates tabs.